WP2 files of Beit Terezin
Files and Documents compiled by Beit Terezin and edited by EHRI to be part of the Terezin Research Guide.
- Ellinger Elsa, 000.001.0
  aliat hanoar; Ellinger Elsa
  - 000.001.1
- Auerbach Sara, 000.002.0
  personal document; correspondence; Correspondence; Auerbach Sara; Auerbach Yossi
  - 000.002.1
    personal document; correspondence; Auerbach Sara; Auerbach Yossi
  - 000.002.2
- Albright Madeleine, 1943; 000.003.0
  personal record; letter; article; Beit Terezin; Alibright Madeleine; Paul Eppstein
  - 1943, 000.003.1
  - 1943, 000.003.2
  - 1943, 000.003.3
  - 1943, 000.003.4
  - 1943, 000.003.5
- A family Auerbuch, 000.004.0
  family tree; letter; Auerbuch
  - 000.004.1
  - 000.004.2
- Adler Yvonne, 000.005.0
  letter; Adler Yvonne
  - 000.005.1
- Oppenheimer Lore (Peis Lore), 1941; 000.006.0
  diary; Latvia; Oppenheimer Lore; Peis Lore
  - 1941, 000.006.1
- Ordner Berthold, 1943; 000.007.0
  personal record; exhibition; sculpture; sketches; interview; diary; Visual arts; Drawings; Ordner Berthold; Ordner Olga; Ginz Petr
  - 1943, 000.007.1
    personal record; exhibition; sculpture; sketches; interview; diary; Ordner Berthold; Ordner Olga; Ginz Petr
  - 1943, 000.007.2
  - 1943, 000.007.3
  - 1943, 000.007.4
  - 1943, 000.007.5
- Opfermann G. Charlotte, 000.008.0
  Freizeitgestaltung; Propaganda; Children and youth; International Committee of the Red Cross; Terezin; Opfermann G. Charlotte
  - 000.008.1
    Freizeitgestaltung; Terezin; Opfermann G. Charlotte
- Sas Andreas, 2011; 000.009.0
  memory; holocaust; Andreas Sas
  - 2011, 000.009.1
- Aurednicek Anna, 001.000.0
  memory book; Terezin; Aurednicek Anna
  - 001.000.1